Office of the City Government, Tangshan,
Hebei, China, July 5, 2007
Dear Congratulations!
We are pleased to tell you that you have won the high school speaking competition about
New Tangshan.
Your speech was heard by a group of five judges,
all of whom agreed that it was the best one
this year.
Your parents and your school should be very proud of you.
Next month, the city will open a new park to honor those who died in the terrible disaster.
The park will also honor those who helped the survivors.
Our office would like to have you speak to the park visitors on July 28 at 11 a.
m.
As you know, this is the day the quake happened 30 years ago.
We invite you to bring your family and friends on that special day.
Sincerely, Zhang Xia.